EARN:
Yo, we should probably
get moving.
You know,
the 75 about to be crazy.
Oh, and your fit's on the table.
Yeah.
Hey, man,
if you want this money,
we need this college fan base.
And, you know,
first it's this,
then it's Spring Fling,
and that's $60K, guaranteed.
You heard me, right?
Nigga, I heard you.
$60K.
You do realize I'm trying
to make you more money?
-That's how I make money.
-Look, no shade,
but we both got different
standards of living, a'ight?
-Yeah, that's true,
but obviously...
-Oh!
-Oh, fuck, man!
Tracy, man, what'd I tell you
about breaking in
my goddamn apartment, man?
This .38 almost sliced your ass.
But, nigga,
you know I'm staying here.
Yeah, but what happened
to "one week," Tracy, man, huh?
One week was months ago.
Man.
You know what?
Whatever, man. Whatever.
Where y'all going?
We're going somewhere not fun.
We're leaving right now.
It's-it's... We got to leave.
That's funny.
-Right now.
'Cause I ain't asked when.
I asked where.
Man, we doing a show.
At Statesboro. For free.
TRACY:
Yo, let me roll, man.
You need security, right?
Look, all I need
is a hotel floor, bruh.
EARN:
We're not staying in a hotel.
Plus, don't you have to tell
your P.O. if you leave?
Damn, yo, you Fulton
County Police or something?
Yo, hold on, hold on.
Bring it back, man.
What you mean, no hotel?
Hey, Earn.
You're not allergic
to jicama, are you
I don't... No.
I don't know. Listen...
-Cool.
-It's not a hotel, per se,
but-but I think
it might be better. Huh?
-Oh, wait.
Th-That's the girl
when both our phones died.
Exactly.
And I found her on Instagram.
And guess what? She love you.
And she runs the Pajama Jam.
Okay, we can just stay
with her and pocket the money
from the hotel.
Ooh. She cute as hell, too, boy.
You stay trying to be slick.
Man, I am slick.
Her roommate?
Treasurer.
That means
Spring Fling next year.
-That's, like...
probably more than $60K
if I can, you know,
sweet-talk her.
All right, man. We'll see.
You know, any bad bitch
with over 3K followers,
it could be tough.
You know,
she got an unrealistic worldview
on how the world works.
She only got,
like, 300 followers.
That's even weirder.
See.
Oh, found my fork.
-Yo, I'm ready.
-Hey, hey, hey, man.
-Oh, I'm ready, too. All right.
-Yeah.
Let's do this, baby.
Oh.
We're...
we're not gonna have
enough room.
And we're leaving right now.
Nigga, I'm ready right now.
Yeah, man.
$200 for security right here.
-Bring all black, boy.
-Say no more.
Come on, man, we're leaving.
Oh, shit,
let me get my jacket, bro.
("Patty Cake"
by Kodak Black playing)
* Sniper Gang *
* Yeah, I like
this lil' beat right here *
* Yeah,
this a nice little beat *
* I'm sippin' on Belaire *
* My chick from Bel-Air *
* My whip from Germany *
:
* I'm cooler than LL *
* I'm sippin' on Belaire *
* My chick from Bel-Air *
* My whip from Germany *
* I'm cooler than LL *
* I clap a nigga *
* Like patty cake *
* I clap a nigga
like patty cake *
* I'm swaggin', I got flavor *
* I got sauce, call me Ragu *
* I love my baby girl *
* Pussy bald, call her Caillou *
* I clap a nigga
like patty cake *
* Yeah, that way *
* I'm 'bout to grab the Wraith *
* I'm 'bout to grab the key *
I think somebody tailing us.
* Snatch your baby girl
and skeet all on her face *
Oh, no, we good, we good.
They turning, they turned.
It's all good. My bad.
* It's either I win or you lose
'cause I won't accept... *
This it?
Yeah. We made it.
-This place kind of stinks.
-Damn.
ALFRED:
The fuck?
-Yeah, man. Shit.
A1. That's a good sign.
Hi. Uh...
does Violet live here?
-Hey, guys.
-Oh.
-Hey.
Hi. I'm Violet.
'Sup.
VIOLET:
Oh!
-I see you brought one extra.
-EARN: Yeah.
That's Tracy. Uh, he won't be
staying here, though.
-I think he's staying
with family.
Nah, nah. I'm staying here.
We can find space.
Cool.
-Great.
-VIOLET: Okay, come in.
Find space.
Okay, guys,
just make yourselves at home.
Uh, so, you guys
remember Erika, right?
-Oh, yeah.
-Yeah. And, uh, you met Honey.
EARN:
Mm-hmm.
So, you two can sleep
in Erika's room,
and Tracy, you can sleep here.
TRACY:
All right, cool.
You got cameras
around the perimeter?
-Uh...
-I'm Paper Boi's security.
He's not really security,
but he'll be fine.
Hey, uh, let me show you
where you're sleeping.
All right.
Hey, you need a hand, big dog?
-ALFRED: I'm good, bruh.
TRACY:
Okay.
Nigga, are you eating
chocolate chips?
Yeah, bruh.
Mmm.
You can sleep
on the bed with me.
No, no, that's cool.
I can sleep over here.
Don't be stupid.
Come here.
Come on.
All right.
Yeah.
See?
This is nice.
Mm
Can I tell you something?
I had a dream about you.
We were holding each other,
naked, by this river,
and you were
this beautiful white crane.
And I was
this magnificent crocodile.
And we were just laying there.
-Hmm.
-Holding each other for warmth.
And then I ate you.
There was blood everywhere.
And then this,
like, intense light
just shot through my belly.
And I knew that meant
that we were connected.
I knew this would happen.
Eventually.
ALFRED:
Mm-hmm.
Hey, what's up, team Paper Boi?
-Don't be rolling up
on my mans like that, bruh.
-All right, man.
-EARN: Hey.
We know them.
They just performed.
What was that all about?
VIOLET:
Oh, my God. I'm such a fan.
-I loved your mixtape.
-You're crushing
this shit tonight, man.
-Thanks, man.
-That's good shit.
-You want to get, like,
a picture or something?
Like those pajamas.
-Yeah, you know.
-Yo, that was a great show.
-Good for a college set.
This kid's killing it.
Clark, you killed that tonight.
Oh, thanks, man.
Yo, y'all were dope, too.
I like the outfits, man.
Y'all trying to get lit with us?
No, man, we gonna hang back
tonight.
-Come on.
-Look, I could use some weed
though, like, bad. Come on.
-Uh, I don't think we...
-CLARK: Dang, bro.
I'm sorry about that.
We do got bottles
in the greenroom, though.
Carson Flex gonna pull up.
-VIOLET: Oh, yeah, we'll hang.
-Oh, yeah.
-She would be great.
-You can go with her.
-CLARK: Thanks, man.
-Yep, all right.
-Yeah, I'm-a find you, man.
CLARK:
Generous, man. Thank you.
Catch you guys later.
VIOLET: Don't have
too much fun without me.
-Hey.
-I'm about to hit the field,
all right?
-Yeah.
You need me,
just give me the signal.
Hit it from here to there.
-You already know.
-Mm-hmm. Yeah.
-Hey, man.
-Appreciate you.
-For sure, baby.
This nigga really think
he a bodyguard.
ALFRED:
Yeah.
He's just trying to earn his
money. I can understand that.
WOMAN:
You really showed up.
I'm sorry. We have a lot
of artists bail on us,
so thank you so much
for coming out.
Oh, no. It's all good.
Thank you.
Well, uh, this is
-my girl, Elise.
She's majoring
in modern literature,
and she's actually
writing a paper on you.
What, like, a Paper Boi paper?
-Yeah, yeah.
All right.
-I can feel that.
-That's what I'm talking about.
-You're very aware
of your words.
You're the only rapper
doing that right now.
I appreciate that.
Yo. Should we save Alfred?
Nah. No, that's good for him.
I haven't seen him smile
in a while.
-He needed that.
If I'm worried about anybody,
I'm worried about that nigga.
DARIUS:
Uh
Oh.
You know that Clark County dude?
-Industry plant.
-Yes, I've been saying that.
-For sure, for sure.
Yeah. No, I mean,
it's obvious.
What the fuck?!
Are you fucking kidding me, man?
I saw that shit, bro!
No. Okay, just stay.
-ALFRED: Yeah, I'm good, man.
-EARN: Just, I'm-a check this.
-I'm-a check this out.
-VIOLET: He was looking at
-those skimpy-ass whores.
I wasn't asking you.
What the fuck you think
he's supposed to do?!
You think you're the only one?
Oh, after I bring all
of y'all into my house.
TRACY: Listen, bitch, keep
your hands off of me for real.
-Do it again,
see what the fuck happens.
-VIOLET: I'm not scared of you.
-Bitch...
You fucking broke-ass
security guard.
* You're nothing but a dirty,
dirty old man *
* You do your thinking
with a one-track mind *
* Clean up your rap,
your story's getting dusty *
* Wash out your mouth, your lies
are getting rusty... *
-Whoa!
You all right?
Yo, you okay?
Oh, damn. Shit.
I knew her ass was crazy, man.
I told you, man. What happened,
yo
Nothing, nothing.
Oh, my eye.
-Hey, she slapping the shit
out of you ain't nothing, man.
I told you her fucking ass was
crazy, man. What happened?
-Yo, we should...
-VIOLET: Those fucking niggas
-was trying to get me!
-We got to... we got to go now.
-VIOLET: Yes!
-We need to leave right now.
Hey, Paper Boi. What's up, man?
What the fuck, man?
What's the issue
-Just chill, you guys.
-Man, we standing
right here, nigga.
-What y'all do
-EARN: Stop it. Go, go.
-It wasn't us. It was, um...
-Come on, man.
What we running from? I don't
even know why we running
-from these niggas, man.
Why are we running
from them, man?
Dude, you can't do shows
in a hospital, man.
-They ain't gonna do shit.
-Hey! I'm talking to you.
-Watch your tone. Relax. Relax.
-No, fuck this dude, man.
-I-I'm gonna take care of this.
-Hell no.
Relax. It's cool.
Okay, listen.
We're all here to have
a good time. Black people.
Just non-violent.
We're trying to...
-TRACY: Bitch!
-ALL: Oh!
Run, nigga, run!
-Run! Run! Run!
Thank you, man.
!
Oh!
ALFRED: What the fuck
are we running from?
-Let's go.
Oh, shit.
That shit was crazy!
Me and Paper Boi!
-ALFRED: Yeah, man.
I can't believe y'all got me out
here like this, man.
Sweating through silk. Shit.
I'm looking like
a goddamn peasant, man.
All I know is that girl Violet
better not touch my weed.
That's all I know.
-Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
-Fuck, bruh. Yo, yo. Come on.
Oh, shit, come on.
Come on. What the fuck?
-All right, man. Goddamn.
TRACY:
Come on.
All this fucking running. Shit.
-Fuck, man.
-We got to get off campus.
Violet knows everybody.
Look, all I know is
I need to find some weed,
or I'm gonna lose my shit, man.
DARIUS: Wait a minute.
Y'all smell that?
What is it?
-Sniff. I mean, use your...
Certain hats, weed.
Yeah.
Citronella.
This way.
Fuck, man.
Holy shit.
You're fucking Paper Boi.
-Yeah.
-That explains the citronella.
What are you doing here, man?
Are those silk pajamas?
Yeah, man, I was...
I was performing at Pajama Jam.
The what?
Forget it, man.
Hey, y'all got weed?
Yeah, yeah, fuck yeah,
we got weed.
We got fuckin',
fuckin' smoking with Paper Boi.
Hell yeah, man.
Y'all on them Backwoods?
We got some other shit in the
house, too. We'll smoke you out.
Thank you. Thank you,
thank you, thank you.
Hell yeah.
-ALFRED:
Oh, what the fuck was that?
It's all good. It's just
some pledges, you know?
Newbies got to pay the price,
right?
Hey, uh, here, come on.
-Let's go. Let's go.
-Yeah.
Hey. Paper Boi's here. Come on.
*
(distant, indistinct
crowd chatter)
Man, this shit is bugged
the fuck out, bruh.
Man. But I like
what y'all doing here, bruh.
You don't give no fucks.
Hey, yo, I just...
I got to tell you, man.
You're like... one-one
of my two favorite rappers.
You know, you and Post Malone?
Yo, that Postal mixtape--
that changed my shit up, man.
Hey, man, is that...
is that an elephant rifle?
Uh... yeah.
Yeah, a bunch of the alumni
send guns to the frats.
A lot of them are in the NRA.
Oh, okay.
I was... Word. I was thinking
about joining the NRA.
Y'all are crazy.
We have a whole gun room.
Wait.
We got a few of these, too.
DARIUS:
Oh, shit.
Hell yeah.
Y
-TRACY: I'm trying
to see that shit.
-No, go ahead.
-Yeah.
-Come on with it.
Whoa.
Excuse me.
(indistinct chatter, laughing
continuing in distance)
Oh, yeah, man,
like I was saying, though, yo.
Yeah, a lot of us
are from the South.
I'm, like, a really big UGK fan.
Pimp C, like, one
of the last real prophets, man.
That was like the-the
Crime Mob, D4L, Maceo days.
Yeah, those were classic.
So you into snap music?
Man.
You remember that song, um...
* The bubble gum. *
-Yeah, that was my shit.
* Laffy Taffy. *
Yeah, my cousin used
to always play that shit.
Hmm.
PRESCOTT:
Matter of fact, hold on.
All right, pledges,
get the fuck up!
Gonna do this dance
for our new friends!
* Girl, shake that laffy taffy *
* That laffy taffy,
shake that laffy taffy *
Snap, y'all!
* Girl, shake that laffy taffy *
* That laffy taffy,
that laffy taffy *
* Oh, oh *
* I'm lookin'
for Mrs. Bubble Gum *
* I'm Mr. Chik-O-Stick *
-* I wanna *
-* Dun dun dunt, oh *
-* 'Cause you so thick... *
* 'Cause I stay so hard *
* You can suck me
for a long time... *
All right, uh, stop, y'all!
* This a candy store *
Uh, I got to go give
these pledges a mud bath.
Uh, y'all need anything
from the fridge?
-We good, man.
-Yeah, we're good. Thank you.
PRESCOTT:
All right. Yeah, cool, man.
Move out!
EARN:
Oh...
Tonight, man...
Tonight was some bullshit.
Yeah.
I know. Uh...
I think we need
to talk about the real problem.
Yes.
Thank you.
Tracy's got to go, man.
Oh, shit, nigga, I'm talking
about your ass.
What?
What are you talking about?
-Man, you gonna
act like tonight wasn't a bunch
of your bad decisions?
Did you not see Tracy
throw a girl down
-I saw it.
And it happened after
she threw a cup at me
for talking
to another broad, man.
And speaking of which,
that bitch--
man, that bitch was crazy
from the start, man.
And you knew that.
And you still put me
in the same room with her ass
so you could save the same
amount of money I would
have made in an hour
or less off the block.
Tracy escalated
a harmless situation.
: Bro.
-You saw that, bruh.
Nothing was about to happen
until something happened.
I've been talking
to Clark County's manager, man.
About what?
The fuck you think, Earn?
Managing me.
Actually managing me, man.
Shit I could be getting,
shit I should be getting
out here.
Look, you family, man, and I'm
trying to ride with you,
but sometimes that shit
ain't enough, bro.
'Cause money is important.
I see exactly what's happening
out here.
It's getting colder,
it's getting harder to eat.
I need shit, Lottie needs shit.
You need shit.
I gotta make my next moves
my best moves, man, so...
Something gotta shake.
I don't think
you're cut out for it.
*
-TRACY: Oh... shit, boy.
-ALFRED: The fuck.
Fuck, no, man.
What the fuck is all this shit?
-That's fucked up, bruh.
-Fuck, bro.
That's fucked up, bruh.
For real.
No, goddamn it. God, man!
Al, just chill.
Damn it, man.
My car and shit, man.
Fucking college bitches.
Who the fuck are we
dealing with, man?
Look at all our shit
on the fucking lawn, man!
-DARIUS: Oh, God, bro.
Oh, fuck no, man!
Look at this shit.
They cut up all my shit!
Goddamn!
And of course
my fucking weed gone.
DARIUS:
Oh.
-Goddamn, let me see that, bruh.
-TRACY: Oh, shit.
-Not the kicks, bruh.
Damn, I couldn't even
be mad at that.
That's kind of...
it's impressive.
Huh.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God,
these fucking hos, man.
Fucking hate these fucking
college hos. Shit!
Where's my laptop?
Violet.
Violet!
TRACY: Ah, shit.
This nigga losing it, man.
-Violet, open this fucking door!
-DARIUS: Hey, Earn.
Violet! Violet!
-Open this door.
-Earn, it's not really
that serious.
Don't fucking touch me, man.
Yo! Violet! Violet!
That's your cousin, bro.
Earn, look, man.
Ain't nobody in there, bro.
Nobody's there; they gone.
-Nah, somebody's in there.
-Look, we'll just go back home.
They're gonna open
this fucking door.
-We'll just figure this out.
-Oh!
-Yo, Earn. Earn, man.
Earn! Earn, Earn, Earn, man.
-Hey, man, I got you.
-Hey, man, let's go, man.
-You'll get your stuff back.
-Let's go, man. Earn!
-It's cool.
-Man, don't do this
to me, nigga.
-TRACY: I'm on probation!
Open this fucking door!
ALFRED: I'm leaving with
or without your ass, man.
-Come on, man.
-Get your ass home.
DARIUS:
Earn. Come on, man.
Fuck that nigga.
I'm out, man.
TRACY:
That shit was crazy, huh?
Earn?
Bruh, you pulling
that fire alarm on 'em?
Now, that shit was fucked up,
my nigga.
You ain't have to do 'em
like that, man.
:
For real.
Yo, this nigga
was kicking the...
:
kicking the door
and shit...
Oh, fuck, man.
What made you go like that, bro?
Kickin' the door?
What, you think a woman gonna
open the door
for you, kickin' the door
like that, bro?
Tracy, could you do me a favor
and stop talking?
I'm not in the mood.
"I'm not in the mood."
Yo, man. Your little cuz
got a temper, man.
You need to watch out
for that one.
You got to watch out for me?
Nigga, this is your fault.
Yeah. It was me
that made them girls crazy.
Nigga, it was.
Were you there?
Hey, both of y'all, chill.
Did you steal that?
:
Goddamn!
Yo, is you the campus police?
Let me see your badge.
Let me see it.
Bang!
Nigga, it's old as fuck, bruh.
You can't even put a bullet
in this thing.
Look at his face, man.
He's scared as hell, boy.
Yo, pull this car over,
so I can fight this nigga.
-ALFRED: Earn.
-Yeah.
Who are you...?
Oh, he playin', right?
Pull the car over.
-Earn, relax, man.
-Al, pull the fucking car over.
-You better get your cousin out.
-So I can beat this nigga's ass.
-Yeah, beat your dumb ass.
-Your fucking dumb country ass.
-Ooh, I want to see
-that shit, man.
-Pull the fucking car over.
Bruh, if this car stop,
I'm-a give you
-these fucking hands, bruh.
-Nigga, I wish it would stop.
-I don't give a fuck.
-Earn, man.
-I'm-a turn your ass...
-I'll knock you the fuck...
I'm so sick and tired
of your fat fucking mouth!
-Open... open this...
-Oh, hey, man. No, no, Earn.
-Pull the fucking car over, man!
-Pull... Yeah, pull the fucking
car over, so I can beat
this nigga's ass!
-All right, all right, let's go.
-Yeah.
DARIUS:
Oh, shit.
Come on, man up.
Come on, dawg.
Nigga.
Come on, man.
Stop playing, dawg.
Get in the car.
TRACY: Come on, man. I don't
want to do all this, bruh.
Come on.
Stop playing with me, man.
Yo! Stop fucking playing
with me, man!
Yeah.
For real?
-EARN: Yeah, yeah, nigga.
I told you to stop fucking
with me, man!
-ALFRED: Tracy, man.
-It's your fucking cousin, man.
-It's not my fault, bruh.
-Come on, man. Come on.
-This nigga, man.
-ALFRED: Come on, man.
TRACY:
That's your fucking cousin, man.
EARN:  You want
to fuck with me, nigga?
What?
-Come on, nigga.
What's up
DARIUS:
Oh! Shit.
Goddamn.
* Oh, doh, doh, doh *
* Doh, doh, doh-doh *
*
-* Ooh, ooh *
-* Or am I *
-* Ooh *
*
-* Ooh, ooh *
* I have a woman *
* And I know *
* She's no good *
* But still
I keep my head up high *
* And try to do the things
that a good man should *
* Whoa, oh *
*
-* Ooh *
* Am I a good man? *
* Ooh *
*
-* Ooh *
* Am I a fool? *
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH